

# BRANDON SHRADER

Jack of All Trades UI/UX, 3D Modeling, Branding & More.

## **ABOUT**

An unconventional, self-taught 3D Generalist with 7+ years of experience in creative direction between a multitude of diverse mediums. Professionally played eSports for two world renowned gaming orgainizations, while leading multiple time-sensitive team projects. I'm a charasmatic soul with passion for creativity and direction. I can work efficiently alone on multiple projects and/or work effectively with a group of other colleagues.



#### **EXPERIENCE**

## 3YR 2019-Now

## **3D GENERALIST**

#### Self Employed / Canton, OH

- Attract 1,000+ unique customers in my personal marketplace for products ranging from 3D Models, Props, Ready-to-Use Unity 3D Assets, and PBR Materials & Textures.
- Coordinate with 150+ clients requesting Custom Modeling, Texturing, Rigging, Animation, and Unity 3D Game Logic.
- · Conceptualized, Directed and Composed original Character Designs, Environments, and Props for personal projects.

## 1YR 2019-2020

# **TEAM LEAD & ESPORTS PLAYER**

#### 100 Thieves / Los Angeles, CA

- Lead and organize a team of professionals to a common goal, while solving real time problems along the way. Evalutate their performance and adjust accordingly.
- Plan, concept, and execute real time strategies to overcome obstacles, with myself and my team to obtain a common goal. Document, and professionally produce content around said goal.
- · Utilize my abilities to, compete, overcome, and proceed through any obstacles while maintaining a professional brand outlook, and further push this through social media.

## **6MO** 2019-2019

## **CONTENT CREATOR & ESPORTS PLAYER**

## Team Liquid / Los Angeles, CA

- · Create interactive, entertaining, and engaging content around the brand. Work with other professionals in this aspect to engage an audience and further spread the brand's name and identity.
- Perform at my highest level possible, among other professionals to achieve a common goal. Practice, and refine my skills I have to obtain said goal.



## **EDUCATION**

## 3.5YR 2016-2019

## ADVERTISING & GRAPHIC DESIGN

## Columbus College of Art & Design / Columbus, OH

• Completed work towards Bachelor of Arts (B.A) Interactive & Graphic Art. Majored in Advertising & Graphic Design, Minored in Film & Studio Photography.



## **SKILLS**

Blender 3D Unity 3D Figma Rigging Animation **Product Rendering** Substance Painter Hardsurface / Organic Modeling Concept Art Game Design / Development Graphic Design Motion Graphic Studio & Film Photography Film Development

Branding & Logo Design UI / UX Design Advertising Marketing Team Management Team Direction Art Direction Project Management Entertainment **Content Creation** Videography / Video Editing Social Media Management





Cibolo, TX, USA



